{
  "data": {
    "title": "JavaScript Flashcards",
    "cards": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What language are Express apps written in?",
        "hint": "It starts with a \"J\"",
        "answer": "JavaScript",
        "set": 1
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What is one way a website can store data in a user's browser?",
        "hint": "They are delicious with milk",
        "answer": "Cookies",
        "set": 1
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What is a common way to shorten the response object's name inside middleware?",
        "hint": "It has the same abbreviation as \"resolution\"",
        "answer": "res",
        "set": 1
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "How many different values can booleans have?",
        "hint": "Think: binary",
        "answer": "2",
        "set": 1
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Which HTML element can contain JavaScript?",
        "hint": "It starts with an \"s\"",
        "answer": "<script>",
        "set": 1
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "あ",
        "hint": "",
        "answer": "A",
        "set": 2
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "え",
        "hint": "",
        "answer": "E",
        "set": 2
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "い",
        "hint": "",
        "answer": "I",
        "set": 2
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "う",
        "hint": "",
        "answer": "U",
        "set": 2
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "お",
        "hint": "",
        "answer": "O",
        "set": 2
      }
    ],
    "sets": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "name": "JavaScript"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "name": "Hiragana"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "name": "JavaScript"
      }
    ]
  }
}